<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="termsConditions">
<![CDATA[<b>Terms and Conditions On Use</b><br /><br /><b>The Terms and Conditions on Use herein are made to have effect on 1st October 2014.</b><br />You agree that by browsing, viewing, accessing, downloading, uploading or using (collectively referred to as “use” or “using”) any applications (including mobile applications) made available by BigC-Connect, the BigC-Connect website or any BigC-Connect service (collectively referred to as the “Service” or "Services"), that you agree to be bound by these terms and conditions on use including any future amendments, modifications or additions in respect of such Services (the "Terms”) which Services are under the control or ownership of BigC-Connect, a business registered in Singapore.  The description “BigC-Connect” as used throughout the Terms shall include the owners, directors, shareholders, managers, officers, employees and agents of BigC-Connect and its related business entities.<br />
These Terms set out your rights and obligations when you use any of the Services of BigC-Connect and that if you do not agree to any of the Terms then you shall immediately cease any use of the Services.<br />
In addition to the Terms there may be other terms and conditions that may apply to the use of any BigC-Connect applications (including mobile applications) or any information, materials, products or services that may appear on the Services and that you agree to be bound by these other terms and conditions in addition to the Terms.<br />  
BigC-Connect may, in its sole and absolute discretion, change or modify the Terms at any time, and such changes or modifications shall be effective immediately upon posting to this Site. Your use of any Services after such changes or modifications have been made shall constitute your acceptance of the Terms as last revised.<br />
BigC-Connect reserves the right in its sole and absolute discretion at any time to suspend, terminate or disable your access to your account or accounts of any of the Services or to the use of any Services without assigning a reason and without giving notice and without any liability whatsoever and howsoever to you. <br />
BigC-Connect maintains access to and can monitor all information, opinions, data, media, postings, materials, images or other content (collectively “Content”) that you submit, upload, transmit, make available or display on any Service (collectively “Your Content”) and reserves the right at any time to edit, copy, retain, delete, block or completely remove Your Content that may be posted on any of the Services.<br />
Nothing in these Terms shall be deemed to create or confer any 3rd party rights or benefits and the same are excluded to the fullest extent possible.  No person other than you and BigC-Connect will have any right to enforce these Terms against any person, and you may not delegate, assign or transfer these Terms or any rights or obligations under these Terms, by operation of law or otherwise. 
<br /><br />
<b>Terms of a General Application to a user of a BigC-Connect Service</b>
<br />You must be of an age where you can be legally bound by the Terms before you may use the Services or alternatively your parent or guardian must agree to be bound by the Terms on your behalf, which will be assumed when you use the Services.<br />
You are responsible for any activity that occurs through your account. You may choose to use your actual name or you may choose to remain anonymous when operating your account and use a fictitious name or description. Any username that is used for an account may be suspended or removed in the sole and absolute discretion of BigC-Connect.<br />
All information that you provide about yourself to BigC-Connect shall be true and accurate at all times and that you shall update any information that you have given to BigC-Connect as and when necessary so as to maintain the truthfulness and accuracy of such information. BigC-Connect does not collect, use or store personal data and any personal data that is provided by you when you use the Services is purely voluntary on your part.<br />
You shall not, when using the Services, post or encourage the posting of Content which may be considered to be defamatory; disparaging of a particular race, language, religion, practice or gender; discriminatory; illegal; infringing; violent; lewd or of an anti-social nature; nude or partially nude; pornographic; sexually suggestive; or other content of a similar nature.<br />
You shall not, while using the Services, engage in behaviour which will cause distress or discomfort to other users of the Services.<br />
You shall refrain from revealing information of a private or confidential nature that may be misused by other users of the Services.<br />
You shall not use the Services for any illegal, infringing, unauthorized or criminal purpose and that your use of the Services shall comply with all laws, rules and regulations governing your use of the Services.<br />  
You shall be solely responsible for your own conduct and of all Content that you post and for the use of any of the Services.<br />
You shall not use the Services for commercial or non-profit purposes and you shall not be permitted to advertise or promote any business, product or service whether of a commercial or of a non-profit nature.<br />
You shall be solely responsible in your dealings and communication with other users of the Services and that BigC-Connect shall not be responsible for or liable to any user of a Service in respect of the conduct of any user of a Service.  All users of a Service are expected to conduct themselves in a respectful and lawful manner.<br /> 
You acknowledge that BigC-Connect does not endorse, support, represent or guarantee the completeness, truthfulness, accuracy or reliability of any Content posted by any user of the Services including whether such Content may be offensive, harmful, inaccurate, defamatory, discriminatory, unlawful, criminal, illegal, or otherwise of a nature that may be unacceptable to another user of the Services and that BigC-Connect shall not under any circumstances be responsible or liable in any way whatsoever and howsoever for any Content of any user of a Service.<br />
You acknowledge that there may be links from the Services, or from communications you receive from the Services, to 3rd party web sites or features. There may also be links to 3rd party web sites or features in materials, images or comments within the Services. The Services also include 3rd party content that BigC-Connect does not control, maintain or endorse. Functionality on the Services may also permit interactions between the Services and a 3rd party web site or feature, including applications that connect the Services or your account on the Services with a 3rd party web site or feature. BigC-Connect has no control of any of these 3rd party web services or any of their content. You expressly acknowledge and agree that BigC-Connect is in no way responsible or liable for any such 3rd party services or features. You may choose, at your sole and absolute discretion and risk, to use applications that connect the Services or your account on the Service with a 3rd party service (collectively a "3rd party Application") and such 3rd party Application may interact with, connect to or gather and/or pull information from and to your Service profile. By using such 3rd party Applications, you acknowledge and agree to the following: (i) if you use a 3rd party Application to share information, you are consenting to information about your profile on the Services and to Your Content being shared; (ii) your use of a 3rd party Application may cause your personal data and Your Content to be publicly disclosed and/or associated with you, even if BigC-Connect has not itself provided your personal data or Your Content; and (iii) your use of a 3rd party Application is at your own option and risk, and you will wholly indemnify and hold BigC-Connect harmless for activity related to the 3rd party Application.<br />
<br />
<b>Rights of BigC-Connect</b><br />
You, as a user of a Service, hereby grant a non-exclusive, royalty-free, transferable, sub-licensable, worldwide and perpetual licence to BigC-Connect to use Your Content including Content of a private nature that you have posted on a Service.<br />
You acknowledge and accept that BigC-Connect is entitled to place all forms and manner of advertisements, promotions, sponsored content, paid services and materials of a commercial or non-commercial nature in close proximity to or in association with Your Content and accounts. You acknowledge and accept that BigC-Connect shall be entitled to determine the form and manner of such advertisements, promotions, sponsored content, paid services and materials of a commercial or non-commercial nature, in its absolute and sole discretion.<br />
You acknowledge and accept that BigC-Connect shall be entitled to rely on Your Content as a representation and warranty by you that you are the owner of Your Content or have the licence to Your Content and that you have granted BigC-Connect the right to use Your Content in the manner as expressly set out in the Terms.  You further warrant and represent to BigC-Connect that the use by BigC-Connect of Your Content does not violate, misappropriate or infringe on the rights of any 3rd party, including, without limitation, privacy rights, publicity rights, copyrights, trademark and/or other intellectual property rights and any other legal rights and that you will wholly indemnify and hold BigC-Connect harmless.<br />
You acknowledge and accept that the Service contains content owned or licensed by BigC-Connect ("BigC-Connect Content") and that all BigC-Connect Content are protected by various forms of intellectual property rights or ownership rights or other laws. You shall not be permitted to alter, remove, or conceal any copyright, trademark, service mark or other proprietary rights notices incorporated in or accompanying the BigC-Connect Content and that you will not use, distribute, reproduce, modify, adapt, prepare derivative works based on, perform, display, publish, transmit, broadcast, sell, license or otherwise exploit the BigC-Connect Content in any form or manner howsoever and wheresoever.<br />
You acknowledge and accept that the design and layout of the Services along with the text, scripts, graphics, interactive features and the like and the trademarks, service marks and logos contained therein are owned by or licensed to BigC-Connect. The Services are provided to you on an “AS IS WHERE IS” basis for your information and personal use only.<br /> 
You acknowledge and accept that the Services may be interrupted or blocked, including, without limitation, for scheduled maintenance or upgrades, for emergency repairs, or due to failure of telecommunications links and/or equipment or by reason of any 3rd party action or inaction, and that BigC-Connect shall not be liable by reason of such interruption or blockage. You are expected to maintain your own backup of Your Content and cannot rely on the Services for the purposes of the backup or storage of Your Content.<br />
You acknowledge and accept that BigC-Connect will not be liable to you for any modification, suspension, or discontinuation of the Services, or for the loss, modification or damage of Your Content. You also acknowledge and accept that the Services may be subject to unauthorised access by 3rd parties and that Your Content may not be secure.<br />
You acknowledge and accept that Your Content will be accessible by any 3rd party unless you have otherwise restricted access to Your Content.  Your Content shall be treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary and that BigC-Connect shall not be liable for any use or disclosure of Your Content which occur without your consent or knowledge.<br />
You acknowledge and accept that BigC-Connect is granted a perpetual, worldwide, royalty-free, assignable and transferable licence to use Your Content, for any purposes whatsoever, including, without limitation, developing and marketing products and services, without any liability or payment of any kind to you.<br />
You acknowledge and accept that BigC-Connect may modify or adapt Your Content in order to transmit, display or distribute the same over computer networks and in various media and/or make changes to Your Content as are necessary to conform and adapt Your Content to any requirements or limitations of any networks, devices, services or media.<br />
You acknowledge and accept that BigC-Connect reserves the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any of Your Content as BigC-Connect reasonably believes is necessary to (i) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, (ii) enforce the Terms, including investigation of potential breaches, (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, (iv) respond to user support requests, or (v) protect the rights, obligations, property or safety of BigC-Connect, its users and the public.<br />
You acknowledge and accept that BigC-Connect reserves the right to remove Your Content if it is alleged to be infringing or in breach of any of the Terms or of any applicable law or regulation or pursuant to a legal process or governmental request, or at the request of a user of the Services or of a 3rd party, without prior notice, at the sole and absolute discretion of BigC-Connect, and without liability to you. In the event that you have been found to have breached the Terms on more than one occasion, BigC-Connect may also terminate your account without any liability whatsoever to you.<br /><br />
<b>Disclaimer of Warranties and Limitation of Liabilities</b><br />
THE SERVICES, ARE PROVIDED ON A \"WITH ALL FAULTS\", "AS IS WHERE IS", “AS AVAILABLE” AND “WITH NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES AS TO FITNESS FOR PURPOSE, MERCHANTABILITY OR NON-INFRINGEMENT” BASIS.<br /> 
TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMISSIBLE BY LAW, BIGC-CONNECT DOES NOT MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OR ENDORSEMENTS OF ANY KIND WHATSOEVER, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED (WHETHER BY LAW, FACTUALLY OR OTHERWISE), AS TO: (A) THE SERVICES; OR (B) SECURITY ASSOCIATED WITH THE SERVICES OR THE TRANSMISSION OF INFORMATION TO BIGC-CONNECT OR VIA THE SERVICES. IN ADDITION, BIGC-CONNECT HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, QUIET ENJOYMENT, SYSTEM INTEGRITY AND SECURITY, FREEDOM FROM COMPUTER VIRUS AND THE LIKE, AND FREEDOM FROM UNAUTHORISED ACCESS, COLLECTION, USE, DISCLOSURE, LOSS, ALTERATION, MISUSE, DESTRUCTION OF YOUR CONTENT OTHERWISE COLLECTIVELY KNOWN AS HACKING.<br />
BIGC-CONNECT DOES NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT THE SERVICES WILL BE ERROR-FREE OR UNINTERRUPTED; THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED; OR THAT THE SERVICE OR THE SERVER THAT MAKES THE SERVICE AVAILABLE IS FREE FROM ANY HARMFUL COMPONENTS, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, VIRUSES AND THE LIKE.  BIGC-CONNECT DOES NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT IT CAN PREVENT ANY UNAUTHORISED ACCESS, COLLECTION, USE, DISCLOSURE, LOSS, ALTERATION, MISUSE, DESTRUCTION OF YOUR CONTENT WHEN YOU USE THE SERVICES AND YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND ACCEPT THAT BIGC-CONNECT SHALL NOT BE LIABLE IN ANYWAY WHATSOEVER OR HOWSOEVER.<br />
BIGC-CONNECT DOES NOT MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES THAT THE INFORMATION (INCLUDING ANY INSTRUCTIONS) ON THE SERVICES ARE ACCURATE, COMPLETE, OR USEFUL. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK. BIGC-CONNECT DOES NOT WARRANT THAT YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES WILL BE LAWFUL IN ANY PARTICULAR JURISDICTION, AND BIGC-CONNECT SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIMS SUCH WARRANTIES.<br />
BY ACCESSING OR USING THE SERVICES YOU REPRESENT AND WARRANT THAT YOUR ACTIVITIES AND YOUR CONTENT ARE LAWFUL IN EVERY JURISDICTION WHERE YOU ACCESS OR USE THE SERVICES.<br />
BIGC-CONNECT DOES NOT ENDORSE ANY CONTENTAND SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIMS ANY RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY TO ANY PERSON OR ENTITY FOR ANY LOSS, DAMAGE (WHETHER ACTUAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, ECONOMIC, PUNITIVE, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE, KNOWN AND UNKNOWN), INJURY, CLAIM, LIABILITY OR OTHER CAUSE OF ANY KIND OR CHARACTER BASED UPON OR RESULTING FROM ANY USE OF THE SERVICES OR RELIANCE ON ANY CONTENT.<br />
UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES WILL BIGC-CONNECT BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGES OF ANY KIND (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, ECONOMIC, EXEMPLARY, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL WHETHER KNOWN OR UNKNOWN) THAT ARE DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY RELATED TO: (A) THE SERVICES; (B) YOUR USE OF, INABILITY TO USE, OR THE PERFORMANCE OF THE SERVICES; (C) ANY ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN THE SERVICES\' OPERATION; OR (D) ANY DAMAGE TO ANY USER\'S COMPUTER, MOBILE DEVICE, OR OTHER EQUIPMENT OR TECHNOLOGY INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGE FROM ANY SECURITY BREACH OR FROM ANY VIRUS AND THE LIKE, BUGS, TAMPERING, HACKING, FRAUD, ERROR, OMISSION, INTERRUPTION, DEFECT, DELAY IN OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION, COMPUTER LINE OR NETWORK FAILURE OR ANY OTHER TECHNICAL OR OTHER MALFUNCTION, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOST PROFITS, LOSS OF GOODWILL, LOSS OF DATA OR YOUR CONTENT, WORK STOPPAGE, ACCURACY OF RESULTS, OR COMPUTER FAILURE OR MALFUNCTION, EVEN IF FORESEEABLE OR EVEN IF BIGC-CONNECT HAD BEEN ADVISED OF OR SHOULD HAVE KNOWN OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, WHETHER CAUSED IN WHOLE OR IN PART BY NEGLIGENCE, DELIBERATE ACTS OR OMISSIONS, ACTS OF GOD, TELECOMMUNICATIONS FAILURE, OR THEFT OR DESTRUCTION OF THE SERVICE).<br /> 
IN NO EVENT WILL BIGC-CONNECT BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANYONE ELSE FOR LOSS, DAMAGE OR INJURY.<br />
NOTWITHSTANDING WHAT HAS BEEN EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMED IN THE TERMS, YOU AGREE THAT IN THE EVENT YOU INCUR ANY DAMAGES, LOSSES OR INJURIES (COLLECTIVELY “DAMAGES”) THAT ARISE OUT OF THE ACTS OR OMISSIONS OF BIGC-CONNECT, THE DAMAGES, IF ANY, THAT MAY BE PAYABLE TO YOU SHALL BE LIMITED TO THE SUM OF S$100.00 ONLY.<br />
BY ACCESSING THE SERVICE, YOU UNDERSTAND THAT YOU MAY BE WAIVING RIGHTS WITH RESPECT TO CLAIMS THAT ARE AT THIS TIME UNKNOWN OR UNSUSPECTED<br />
BIGC-CONNECT IS NOT RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE FOR THE ACTIONS, CONTENT, INFORMATION, OR DATA OF 3RD PARTIES, AND YOU WHOLLY AND COMPLETELY RELEASE BIGC-CONNECT FROM ANY CLAIMS AND DAMAGES, KNOWN AND UNKNOWN, ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH ANY CLAIM YOU MAY HAVE AGAINST ANY SUCH 3RD PARTIES.<br />
<br />
<b>Indemnification of BigC-Connect by you</b><br />
You agree to defend, wholly indemnify and hold harmless BigC-Connect from and against any and all claims, damages, obligations, losses, liabilities, costs or debt, and expenses (including but not limited to attorney\'s fees on a full indemnity basis) arising from: (i) your use of the Services; (ii) your breach of any the Terms; or (iii) your breach of any 3rd party rights, including without limitation any intellectual property, legal, property, or privacy right. This indemnification obligation will survive these Terms and your use of the Services. You will, at your own cost, cooperate as fully as is required by BigC-Connect in the defence of any claim. BigC-Connect reserves the right to assume the exclusive defence and control of any matter subject to complete indemnification by you, and you will not in any event settle any claim without the prior written consent of BigC-Connect, which consent may be withheld at the sole and absolute discretion of BigC-Connect.<br />
<br />
<b>Arbitration and choice of law</b><br />
You agree that any dispute, claim, misunderstanding or issue arising out of or in connection with or in relation to the Services, the Terms, any rights of privacy or personal data and Your Content, shall be referred to and finally resolved by arbitration in Singapore in accordance with the rules of the Singapore International Arbitration Centre (“SIAC”) which rules are deemed incorporated herein by reference.  The arbitration shall be conducted by a single arbitrator appointed by the President of the Court of Arbitration of the SIAC, at the written request of any party. The arbitration shall be conducted in the English language. Neither party shall challenge the award of the arbitrator, when it has been rendered, in any court of competent jurisdiction and neither party shall challenge the enforcement of the award in any court of competent jurisdiction.  Judgment on the award rendered by the arbitrator may be entered in any court having competent jurisdiction.<br /> 
The Terms and your use of the Services are governed by and shall be construed in accordance with the laws of the Republic of Singapore without giving effect to any conflict of laws principles.<br />
YOU AGREE AND ACKNOWLEDGE THAT ANY CAUSE OF ACTION ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH OR IN RELATION TO THE SERVICES OR THE TERMS OR YOUR CONTENT SHALL BE COMMENCED WITHIN ONE (1) YEAR AFTER THE CAUSE OF ACTION ACCRUES, FAILING WHICH SUCH CAUSE OF ACTION SHALL BE DEEMED TO HAVE BEEN PERMANENTLY BARRED AND THE CAUSE OF ACTION WAIVED.<br />
<br />
<b>Marketing to you</b><br />
BigC-Connect may use your information for the purpose of sending you advertising or direct marketing (whether by messaging within the Services, by email or by other means) that offer or advertise our products and services and that of 3rd parties.  You hereby authorise BigC-Connect to provide non-personal data which for the purposes of the Terms shall include your account name and e-mail address or addresses as provided to BigC-Connect to 3rd parties for the purposes of sending advertising and direct marketing.<br />
<br />
<b>General terms</b><br />
Should any of the provisions of the Terms be deemed invalid, unlawful or otherwise unenforceable by an authority of competent jurisdiction, such provision shall be deemed severable and severed from the Terms and the remaining provisions of the Terms shall remain in full force and effect.<br /> 
No waiver of any provisions of the Terms shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such provision or any other provision, and the failure of BigC-Connect to assert or insist upon the strict performance or due performance of any right or provision under the Terms shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision.<br />
The Terms comprise the entire agreement between you and BigC-Connect and governs your use of the Services. The Terms supersede any previous understandings or agreements (whether written or oral) and no course of conduct or trade practice may alter, amend, modify or nullify any of the Terms.<br /> 
BigC-Connect may assign or transfer in whole or in part these Terms or any rights or obligations hereunder without your consent or notice to you.<br /> 
You may, from time to time, make payments to BigC-Connect as part of your use of the Services (including for the provision of the Services or provision of certain additional features within the Services). Specific terms in relation to payments shall be applicable and you shall comply with such terms in relation to the payments as if such terms were provisions of the Terms.<br />
To the extent that that the Terms may be translated to a language other than English, in the event of a conflict as to meaning or effect between the Terms as translated and the Terms in English, the Terms in the English version shall prevail. ]]>
    </string>

</resources>